mymemory.co.uk 2019-11-04

# Privacy Policy | MyMemory

This privacy policy explains how MyMemory uses the personal information we collect about you when you use our website. 

Topics

  * What information do we collect about you?
  * How do we use your information?
  * Marketing
  * Access to your information and correction
  * Links to other websites
  * Changes to our privacy policy
  * How to contact us
  * Cookies
  * List of cookies we collect

## What information do we collect about you?

We collect information about you when you visit our website, register with us, or place an order. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback, signup to our mailing list, or participate in competitions.

Information we may collect includes:

  * Contact information including name, email address, postal address, and telephone number
  * Demographic information such as location, preferences, and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys or offers

Website usage information is collected using cookies. To see the full list of cookies we collect scroll down the page or click here. 

## How do we use your information?

We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account and, if you agree, email you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you. We also use your information collected from the website to personalise your repeat visits to our website.

Whilst MyMemory will not share your information with any third parties, we may utilise your information to provide you with personalised product recommendations via third party platforms.

In processing your order we may send your details to, and also use information from, credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies. 

## Marketing

With your consent we will send you information about products which we hope will be of interest to you. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please update your email preferences by clicking the link in the footer of any marketing email you have received from us, or by contacting our customer support team. 

## Access to your information and correction

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.

## Links to other websites

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies. 

## Changes to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this page. This privacy policy was last updated on 19th May 2018. 

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you.

  * Email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#21525451514e5355614c584c444c4e53580f424e4c)
  * Call us on +44 (0)203 8902558 between Monday to Friday, 10am to 4pm (GMT)
  * Our live chat service is open Monday to Friday, 9am to 4pm (GMT)
  * Write to us at MyMemory Ltd,2 Britannia Place, St Helier, Jersey, JE2 4SU

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

Domain | Name | Information  
---|---|---  
.abmr.net | 01AI | Targeting/Advertising  
.c.paypal.com | sc_f | Paypal  
.facebook.com | fr | Targeting/Advertising  
.mymemory.co.uk | _ga | Google Analytics  
.mymemory.co.uk | _gat | Google Analytics  
.mymemory.co.uk | _gid | Google Analytics  
.paypal.com | KHcl0EuY7AKSMgfvHl7J5E7hPtK | Paypal  
.paypal.com | X-PP-SILOVER | Paypal  
.paypalobjects.com | PYPF | Paypal  
.stats.paypal.com | c | Paypal  
.thefilter.com | FilterUserGuid | Personalisation  
.www.mymemory.co.uk | __mm_checkoutoffer | Personalisation  
.www.mymemory.co.uk | am_promo_notification | Personalisation  
.www.mymemory.co.uk | external_no_cache | Performance / Functionality  
.www.mymemory.co.uk | frontend | Performance / Functionality  
.www.mymemory.co.uk | frontend_cid | Performance / Functionality  
.www.mymemory.co.uk | mailchimp_landing_page | Targeting/Advertising  
.www.mymemory.co.uk | mymemory_devicedetection_cache | Personalisation  
js.gleam.io | _mkra_ctxt | Targeting/Advertising  
pubsub.rtschannel.com | io | Performance / Functionality  
pubsub.rtschannel.com | SERVERID | Performance / Functionality  
ssl.kaptcha.com | k | Performance / Functionality  
wchat.freshchat.com | JSESSIONID | Personalisation  
www.google.com | OTZ | Google Analytics  
www.mymemory.co.uk | DAPROPS | Personalisation
